This is a song for that one person who keeps you
sane, the one who's your anchor. The lights are
bright, but the room is cold Another story
that's burning so
When the world is spinning out of my control
You're the one true thing that I can't hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter You
are the truth My anchor in this crazy youth
They pull us under They push us high They build us
up just to watch us die It's hard to know who you
can trust When all the promises turn to dust
But when the world is spinning out of my control
You're the one true thing that I can't hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter You
are the truth My anchor in this crazy earth
balls.
So let them talk, let them stare As long as you are
standing there I'm not afraid of what's to come I
know where I belong
Cause when the world is spinning out at night
You're the one true thing that I can't hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter, you
are the truth My anchoring is crazier
We love you Chicago